Crooked House is a mystery, crime, thriller film
directed by Gilles Paquet-Brenner.
A private investigator helps a former flame solve the murder of her wealthy grandfather,
who lived in a sprawling estate surrounded by his idiosyncratic family.
Lady Edith de Haviland, played by Glenn Close.
Charles Hayward, played by Max Irons.
Sophia de Haviland, played by Stefanie Martini.
Brenda Leonides, played by Christina Hendricks.
Chief Inspector Taverner, played by Terence Stamp.
Josephine Leonides, played by Honor Kneafsey.
Crooked House is a 2017 mystery film directed by Gilles Paquet-Brenner,
based on Agatha Christie’s 1949 novel of the same name.
A British-American coproduction, the film stars Max Irons, Terence
Stamp, Glenn Close, Gillian Anderson, and Stefanie Martini.
Principal photography began in September 2016, and the film
aired in the UK on Channel 5 on 17 December 2017.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
detective, murder, whodunit, murder mystery.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.